大家好
hey everybody
我的名字是Natemore
my name is natemore
我很高兴今天能在这里谈论
and I'm thrilled to be here today to talk
关于岛上的建筑
about island's architecture
阿斯特罗和你
astro and you
很荣幸能与大家分享
it is such an honor to share
虚拟舞台
the virtual stage
与这样一个令人难以置信的人的阵容
with such an incredible lineup of people
我非常非常兴奋地向你们介绍astro
and I'm really really excited to introduce you to astro
它是一个新的工具，用于建立更快的网站
it's a new tool for building faster websites
astro one pointo在几周前推出。
astro one pointo launched a few weeks ago
但它已经
but it's been
在幕后进行了一年多的工作
well over a year of work behind the scenes
让一切准备就绪
to get everything ready
为了这一刻
for this moment
astro背后有一个不可思议的团队
there is an incredible team behind astro
的维护者和核心维护者
of maintainers and core maintainers
我真的鼓励你去看看我们的社区
and I really encourage you to check out our community
我非常
I'm super
兴奋地展示我们一直在做的事情
excited to show off what we've been working on
并谈谈小岛的架构
and chat about island's architecture
它是一种非常有趣的
it's a really interesting
它是一种非常有趣的方式来解决当前框架中出现的性能瓶颈问题。
way to solve performance bottlenecks that come up with
遇到的性能瓶颈。
the current crop of frameworks
总的来说，我认为 astro 是一种非常有趣的
and overall I think astro is a really fun
总的来说，我认为 astro 是一种非常有趣的、平易近人的网站建设方式
approachable way to build websites
你一定会喜欢的
that you're going to love
对不起，我刚才没听清你的名字
sorry I didn't catch your name earlier
一个典型的网站是这样的
so a typical website looks something like this
你可以看到，我们已经把事情分解为
and you can see we've kind of broken things down
组成的
into components
这确实是大多数
that's really the way that most
开发人员的工作方式
developers work these days
很多组件都是互动的
and a lot of these components are interactive
但其中大部分实际上是静态的
but most of them are actually static
所以有一些组件
so there are some pieces that
需要客户端的javascript
require clientside javascript
但在我看来
but in my mind
但在我看来，这些组件中的大多数都不需要客户端的javascript。
most of these don't need clientside javascript
如果采用传统的方法
with a traditional approach
所有的东西都是一个javascript单体的情况下
where everything is kind of one javascript monolith
你可以在服务器端渲染这个
you might render this on the server side
然后再在客户端进行水化
and then also hydrated on the client
这是一个很好的开发者体验
it's a nice developer experience
在这里，代码是同构的
where the code is isomorphic
而且你只需要写一次
and you're only writing things once
但
but
它在两个地方运行，而且
it's running in 2 places and
你最终会有几百KB的javascript
you end up with hundreds of kilobytes of javascript
其中一些运行在服务器上
some of which runs on the server
然后它也在客户端运行
and thenit also runs on the client
甚至对于
even for
非交互式的作品，也不需要任何
non interactive pieces that really don't need any
客户端上的javascript
javascript on the client
因此，对于Astro
so with astro
我们正在使用一种叫做 "岛屿结构 "的技术
we're using a technique called island's architecture
你可能也听说过部分水化这个词
and you may have also heard the term partial hydration
所以这是一个非常相似的基于组件的体验
so it's a very similar component based experience
甚至使用相同的
even using the same
框架，你已经知道并喜欢这些框架
frameworks that you already know and love
但网站的互动部分被分解为
but interactive pieces of the site are broken down
分成我们所说的岛屿
into what we call islands
所以岛屿基本上是
so islands are basically
在你的静态内容中的微小应用
tiny applications inside of your static content
在Astro中岛屿是递归的
and in astro islands are recursive
岛屿的子代实际上是
and the children of islands are actually
不是你的javascript包的一部分
not part of your javascript bundle
而是嵌入在HTML中
but are embedded in the HTML
这相当于将javascript的总体数量减少了90
what this amounts to is up to a 90
这相当于在整体上减少了90％的javascript
percent reduction in javascript overall
因此，建立伟大的网站
so building great websites
这就是我们在这里的目的
that's what we're all here for
而且它每年都会变得更容易
and it gets easier every year
但在我看来
but in my mind
选择正确的工具从未如此困难
choosing the right tool has never been more difficult
你可以
you can
用静态网站生成器建立一个静态网站
build a static site with a static site generator
如Hugo或levindi
like Hugo or levindi
但这样你就真的
but then you're really
手滚动你自己的客户端javascript
hand rolling your own client side javascript
你可以建立一个传统的单页应用程序
you can build a traditional single page application
但这有很多弊端
but that comes with a lot of downsides
比如
like
糟糕的SEO和性能
poor SEO and performance
你可以用Jamstack模式来减轻这些问题的影响
you can mitigate some of that with the jamstack pattern
你可以通过jamstack模式来缓解一些问题，在这里你要渲染
where you're rendering
渲染服务器，然后将其作为一个
the server and then enhancing it as a
在客户端的单页应用
single page application on the client
或者你可以完全依靠服务器并在请求时
or you can fully lean into the server and
在请求时渲染你的页面
render your pages at request time
所有这些都会带来非常有趣的权衡
all these come with really interesting trade offs
所以静态网站的设计是为了提高客户端的速度
so static sites are designed for speed on the client
但正如我所提到的，你的
but like I mentioned your
和滚动你自己的javascript
and rolling your own javascript
甚至可能建立一个构建管道
and maybe even setting up a build pipeline
它有时是很难操作的
it's pretty difficult to work with sometimes
而spas是为交互性设计的
and spas are designed for interactivity
它们对SEO或性能没有好处
they are not good for SEO or performance
但对于长时间的会议来说，它们可以是非常好的。
but for long sessions they can be really great
jamstack让内容工作变得非常容易。
jamstack makes it really easy to work with content
但我们优先考虑的是我们自己的开发者体验
but we're prioritizing our own developer experience
而不是客户端的性能
over the client side performance
与服务器端渲染的应用程序
and with server side rendered applications
他们的规模
they scale
但
but
但随着规模的扩大，它也有自己的问题
with scale comes its own set problems
因此，这就是我们建立Astro的原因
so this is why we built astro
它是为所有人设计的网络框架
it's the web framework designed for everybody
它很好地平衡了
it strikes a really good balance
在所有的权衡之间
between all the trade offs
上一代工具所做的交易之间取得了很好的平衡
the last generation of tools made
但对于新手来说，它也是非常平易近人的。
but it's also really approachable for newcomers
而且还有强大的
and there are still powerful
的功能供高级用户使用。
features for advanced users to take advantage of
在我看来，这就是现代开发者的体验
in my mind it's the modern developer experience
与
with
我认为这是现代开发者的体验，我们应该以这种方式来建设网站
the way we should have been building websites this
始终如一
whole time
所以Astro从一开始就为速度而设计。
so astro has been designed for speed from the ground up
我们有一个性能的痴迷
we have a performance obsession
我们
we
真正使用岛屿的架构方法
really use the island's architecture approach
来提取你的用户界面
to extract your user interface
到小的独立组件中
into small isolated components
而不是在服务器上渲染一切
so instead of rendering everything on the server
将其发送到客户端并再次进行水化
sending it to the client and hydrating again
我们只把互动的部分发送到客户端
we are only sending the interactive parts to the client
最终的结果是，未使用的javascript
the end result is that unused javascript
不会出现在客户端
never ends up in the client
而且你的网站加载速度更快
and your site loads faster
你会有更快的时间来互动
you'll have a faster time to interactive
以及更好的Lighthouse指标
and much better lighthouse metrics
我们使用所谓的 "水合指令 "来实现这一点。
we do this using what we call hydration directives
所以这是真正的懒惰加载
so this is really lazy loading
作为框架的一个核心功能
as a core feature of the framework
这并不是你必须考虑的事情
and it's not something you have to think about
或以特殊方式编写代码来利用它。
or right code in a special way to take advantage of
我们有客户端负载
we have client load
是一个高优先级的
which is a high priority
并立即加载一个组件
and loads a component immediately
我们有客户端空闲，这是一个中等优先级
we have client idle which is a medium priority
我们会在待处理的工作完成后，立即预加载你的组件。
and we'll preload your component as soon as
待完成的工作
pending work is done
然后，我们有客户端可见，这是非常有趣的
and then we have client visible which is really fun
然后我们有客户端可见，这非常有趣，它将只在你的组件
and this will load your component only
当它出现在屏幕上并实际可见时，才会加载你的组件。
when it comes in and is actually visible on screen
astro是为内容而设计的
astro was designed for content
所以内容是网络的基础
so content is really the foundation of the web
我们
we
我们使建立静态网站变得有趣和简单
make building static sites fun and easy
我们支持HTML标记的页面，并支持mdx。
we support pages in HTML Mark down mdx
我们的文件系统路由与Next js非常相似
we have really similar file system routing to next js
我们通过内置的获取支持使其变得非常容易
and we make it so easy with built in fetch support to
调用任何CMS或端点
call any CMS or endpoint
使用一个熟悉的网络API
using a familiar web API
我们在建造天体时也考虑到了互动性，所以
we also built astro with interactivity in mind so
你不应该
you shouldn't
必须选择你的
have to choose your
元框架的基础上，你喜欢使用
meta framework based on the framework that you like
使用的框架
to use
在astro中，我们是不考虑框架的
with astro we are framework agnostic
所以你可以使用你喜欢的
so you can use your favorite
或者你可以选择一个不同的
or you can pick a different one
并把它放在每个不同的页面上
and put it on every different page
你可以使用你已经喜欢的工具
you can use the tools you already love
我们与Tan Wind Postss SAS整合得非常好。
and we integrate really well with tan wind postss SAS
所有的V生态系统所期望的东西。
all of the things that the v ecosystem expects
astro不仅仅是一个静态网站生成器
astro is not just a static site generator
我们真的设计了它来扩展
we really designed it to scale
所以你可以从
so you can go from
构建时渲染的静态网站
static sites that are rendered at build time
并切换到服务器模式
and switch into server mode
在那里你会根据要求进行渲染
where you're rendering on request
使用 astro ad
with astro ad
你只需一个命令就可以部署到netify上。
you're only one command away from deploying to netify
verselle cloud flair deno，甚至更多。
verselle cloud flair deno and even more
好了
all right
这是一个很好的介绍，也是关于astro的一些背景。
that was a great intro and some background on astro
但现在我想一起建立一些东西
but now I want to build something together
因此，让我们使用我们的Astro项目的脚手架
so let's scaffold out our astro project using our
创建 astro cli
create astro cli
你所要做的就是运行
all you have to do is run
pnpm create astro
并创建一个名为feed comp的文件夹
and let's create a folder named feed comp
我将从一个空项目开始
and I'm going to start with an empty project
我们可以一起走过它
and we can walk through it together
我们将安装依赖性
and we will install dependency
但不创建一个git rifo
but not create a git rifo
然后它会问我们如何设置类型脚本
and it asks us how we want to set up type script
这很好，因为
which is cool because
astro实际上是默认的类型脚本
astro is actually type script by default
所以你根本不需要做任何设置
so there's never any setup that you have to do
在这种情况下，我打算用严格的方式。
in this case I'm going to go with strict
我们得到一些关于如何继续的指示
and we get some instructions on how to continue
让我们看一下生成的文件
so let's take a look at the files that got generated
我们有一个公共目录
we have a public directory
这里是任何
and this is where any
static assets that astro is not going to touch will go
这些将被复制到最终的构建中。
these will just be copied over to the final build
我们有一个源代码
we have a source
页目录
pages directory
这是我们基于文件的路由启动的地方
which is where our file based routing kicks in
然后我们有一个 astro 配置文件
and then we have an astro config file
这个文件最酷的地方是
what's cool about this is
你可能不需要打开这个文件
you probably don't need to open this file
我们有一个命令
we have a command
我们有一个命令行工具，可以为你编辑你的配置
line tool that will edit your config for you
但如果我们看一下index dot astro页面
but if we look at the index dot astro page
它看起来很像HTML
it looks a lot like HTML
而这是因为天体的
and that's because astro
有一种特殊的语法，是HTML的超集
has a special syntax that is a superset of HTML
所以dot astro
so dot astro
你可以在HTML中做的任何事情都可以在这里做
anything you can do in HTML you can do here
但显然我们建立自己的语法是有原因的
but obviously we've built our own syntax for a reason
我们想要的东西是一个真正伟大的混合体。
we wanted something that was a really great mix of
初学者的hdml
hdml for beginners
又有jsx的强大功能的东西
and something that had the power of jsx
表达式的强大功能给专家。
like expressions for experts
所以在我们开始之前，我将会把一个
so before we get started I'm just going to drop a
样式表到我们的公共目录
style sheet into our public directory
然后我们就可以用一个普通的
and then we can just use a regular
链接标签
link tag
主CSS
main CSS
这样看起来就会好一点
and that's looking a little bit better
你可以在Astro中使用的最强大的东西之一
one of the most powerful things you can
最强大的东西之一是我们所说的 "前台事务"。
use in astro is what we refer to as front matter
所以这里的区域是任何服务器端的javascript
so this area up here is any server side javascript
来设置你的模板
that is going to set up your template
因此，我们可以使用像顶层的权重和获取的东西
so we can use things like top level of weight and fetch
和调用任何
and call any
API，我们可能有
API that we might have
和
and
然后我们可以使用类似jsx的表达式
then we can use a jsx like expression
来映射我们所有的发言人
to map over all our speakers
我只是要把发言者的名字放在页面上
and I'm just gonna put the speaker name on the page
你就可以看到今天发言的所有人
and you can see everybody that is speaking today
但在天体中我们可以做的另一件事是
but one other thing we can do in an astrophile is
使用范围风格
use scope style
所以每一种风格
so every style
样式都会是范围性的
in an astrophile is gonna be scope
到该文件中，默认情况下
to that file by default
所以如果我在这里添加一些CSS
so if I add some CSS here
这实际上只是一个范围
this will actually just be scoped
所以这不会从文件中渗出。
so this is not gonna bleed out of the file at all
我们可以做的另一件事
another thing we can do
我提到了基于组件的工作流程
I mention that component based workflow
所以我们可以把它提取到
so we can extract this to
一个组件目录
a components directory
这并不特别，只是惯例
which isn't special as just convention
但我要把这个标题称为
but I'm gonna call this title
嘿
hey
我就把我的h移过去
I'll just move my h one over
和我的样式
and my styles
所以现在我们可以在这里导入
so now up here we can import
我们的标题组件
our title component
然后渲染它
and then render it
像其他组件一样
like any other component
所以我认为将这些扬声器提取到它们自己的组件中会很酷
so I think it would be cool
将这些扬声器提取为自己的组件
to extract these speakers to their own component
所以让我们制作一个扬声器
so let's make a speaker
卡
card
我们要在前台设置一些东西
and we're gonna set up some stuff in the front matter
所以我们要抓取
so we're gonna grab the
至少从我们的天体道具中获取名称
name at least out of our astro props
并输入这些
and to type these
我们所要做的就是写一个叫做props的接口
all we have to do is write an interface called props
这个接口将有一个名字
this will have a name
是一个字符串
which is a string
和项目，后者是
and projects which is
一个字符串的数组
an array of strings
所以，如果我们跳回到这里，导入我们的扬声器卡
so if we jump back here and import our speaker card
我们可以将其替换为
we can replace this with
我们可以用一个组件来代替它，这个组件只是把扬声器作为道具传入。
a component that just passes in the speaker as props
现在我们就有了这个很棒的列表，上面有每个人
now we have this awesome list of everybody
今天的发言
speaking today
我意识到我忘了把它包装成
and I'm actually realizing I forgot to wrap this
用一个无序的列表
in an unordered list
所以我们要这么做
so we're gonna do that
我们的样式也变得更好了
and our styling gets a little better
我还想把我们的样式整理一下
I also want to clean up our styles a little bit
比几分钟后长一点
a little longer than a few minutes later
所以这看起来好多了
so this looks a lot better
希望能给你一个很好的感觉
and hopefully gives you a good sense of
感受到处理数据是多么容易
just how easy it is to work with data
并将其纳入一些带有样式的标记中
and pipe it into some markup with styles
在Astro中
in astro
现在我想这是 astro 的一个秘密的超级能力
now I think this is a secret superpower of astro
你可以在不接触客户端javascript的情况下，获得真正的进展。
that you can get really far without
就能达到很高的境界，而不需要接触客户端的javascript
ever touching client side javascript
但我确实答应过要讲讲这个岛的架构
but I did promise to talk on island's architecture
所以我们现在就开始吧
so let's do that now
所以 astro
so astro
实际上是把小岛的架构模式
actually brings the island's architecture pattern
到每个公司的工作中
to every firm work
而你所要做的就是添加
and all you have to do is add
pnpm 运行 astro 添加你选择的框架
pnpm run astro add the framework of your choice
在这种情况下，我将选择pre act
in this case I'm going to choose pre act
因为我最近非常喜欢pre x信号
because I really like pre x signals lately
所以我们要运行 astro 添加 pre act
so we're going to run astro add pre act
这将安装我们需要的依赖项
and this will install our dependencies that we need
而且我们还会问我们
and we'll also ask us
如果我们想更新我们的配置文件，我们会这样做
if we want to update our config file which we do
这就是它的全部内容了
and that's all there is to it
我们可以开始添加一个preact组件了
we can get started and add a preact component
我们只是要输出一个按钮
and we're just going to export a button
除了一些孩子之外
that except some children
但这并不十分有趣
but that's not very interesting
除非它在我们点击它的时候做些什么
unless it does something when we click it
所以我们要创建一个存储文件
so we're going to create a store file
这将使用新的
and this will use the new
preact信号，这非常酷
preact signals which are very cool
我们将导出一个名为菜单的信号
and we'll export a signal called menu
的信号，开始时是关闭的
that starts out closed
我们还将输出一个切换信号
and we're also going to export a toggle
所以这将切换菜单的值
so this will switch the value of menu
的值切换为打开或关闭
to open or closed
然后，它还将
and then it's also going to
记录
log
我们已经谈了一些
that we've talked something
与当前状态
with the current state
现在，如果我们返回到我们的按钮组件，我们可以导入
now if we go back to our button component we can import
幼儿
toddle
并
and
将其设置为
set this to be the
点击处理程序
click handler
并在这个文件中导入我们的按钮
and back in this file will import our button
我们可以像其他组件一样使用它
we can use it like any other component
除了
except that
你可以看到，我们在这里有这些水化指令
you can see we have these hydration directives here
所以这些操作的每一个组件都是用来发送
so each of these ops are component into sending
到客户端的javascript
javascript to the client
这真的很好，因为你可以精细地
this is really nice because you have granular
控制哪些内容最终会出现在客户端
control over what actually ends up in the client
实际上，我只想说这里的菜单
I'm actually gonna just say menu here
我们已经得到了它，所以如果我们检查我们的控制台
andwe've got it so if we check our console
我们应该能看到
we should be able to see
这个日志切换了很多
that this log toggle a bunch
所以这个切换是有效的
so that toggle is working
现在我们可以把它连接到
and now we can hook it up to
一个菜单
a menu
所以我将创建一个菜单组件
so I'm going to create a menu component
导入菜单
imports bolt the menu
和切换
and toggle
并接受一些子程序
and also take some children
这很有趣
and this is interesting
所以我们要根据菜单的状态，以不同的方式呈现
so we're going to render differently based on
菜单的状态
the state of the menu
所以如果菜单的点值
so if menu dot value
是关闭的，我们将不返回任何东西
is closed we're gonna return nothing
否则，我们将返回
otherwise we're gonna return
在一个侧面
in a side
如果我们点击这个，我们就会切换到
and if we click on this we're gonna toggle
所以这将是背景墙
so this is this will be the backdrop
和
and
这将是主要内容
this will be the main content
而这里将停止传播
and here will stop propagation
这样，切换就不会被触发了。
so that the toggle doesn't get triggered
大家好
hey everybody
我的名字是Nate Mole
my name is nate mole
让我们在这里渲染那个菜单组件
so let's renderthat menu component here
并确保给它注水
and make sure to hydrate it
这可以接受一个数组
and this can take an array
5个项目的数组，这里的第二个参数
of 5 items and the second argument here
第二个参数实际上是一个地图函数
is actually a map function
对不起，我刚才没听清你的名字，我是Bo
sorry I didn't catch your name earlier I'm bo
它需要
that takes
一个地图回调
a map callback
所以我们可以直接返回
so we can just return
夏威夷
Hawaii
与第一页加一
with page I plus one
我们将它包在一个列表中
and we'll wrap it in a list
现在，当我们点击这个
and now when we click this
一个飞出的菜单应该从左边出现
a flyout menu should come from the left
它完全做到了这一点
which it totally does
所以这是一个岛
so this is an island
而这个按钮是一个岛
and this button is an island
它们通过一个共享的信号进行通信
and they are communicating through a shared signal
一切
everything
静态的都会留在你的天体中
and that is static is going to stay in your astrophile
而一切动态的
and everything that's dynamic
或需要一些逻辑的东西
or requires a bit of logic
都会在你的jsx文件中。
is going to be in your jsx files
而你明确地选择加入
and you're explicitly opting in
向浏览器发送javascript，所以
to sending that javascript to the browser so
你可以认为
you can kind of think of
岛屿就像甜甜圈
islands like donuts
有一个外环，有一些互动性
there's an outer ring that has some interactivity
但它里面的一切实际上都是从客户端的HTML中恢复的
but everything inside of it is actually revived from
客户端的HTML
the client side HTML
所以这意味着你的javascript包是
so this means your javascript bundles are
真的非常小
really really small
还有一件很酷的事情我们可以做
and there's one other cool thing we can do
我们实际上可以从Astro传入槽位
we can actually pass in slots from astro
到我们的组件
to our components
而我们这样做的方法是
and the way we do that is
就像你在任何其他astro文件中那样
just like you would in any other astro file
我们要在这里有一个片段
we're gonna have a fragment here
叫做title
that's called title
现在，我们有一个槽
and now that we have a slot
是一个组件的孩子
that is a child of a component
我们在这里接收标题作为一个道具
we receive the title as a prop here
然后我将创建一个标题
and then I'm just going to create a header
我们叫它
we'll call it
导航
nav
我们将使用这个标题
and we'll use that title
然后是一个关闭按钮
and then just a close button
寺庙切换
temple toggle
所以现在当我们点击这个菜单时，我们应该得到
so now when we click on the menu we should get
一个标题
a title
和一个关闭按钮，以及我们所有的页面
and a close button and all our pages
而点击这里却什么也做不了
and clicking here does nothing
点击外面或点击关闭按钮
clicking outside or clicking the close button
完全有效
totally works
总结一下
to wrap up
我认为看看以下内容会非常有趣
I thought it would be really interesting to look at
这背后发生了什么？
what's going on behind the scenes here
那么，这究竟是如何工作的呢？
so how is this actually working
我们必须要看一下我们的HTML。
and we have to look at our HTML for that
所以有一个样式和一个脚本，我们正在注入
so there's a style and a script that we're injecting
这就是整个Astro的运行时间
this is the entire astro run time
它真的很小
it's really tiny
而且
and
我们有这些astro岛的自定义元素
we have these astro island custom elements
所以这些基本上是
so these are basically
加载一些块状的javascript
loading some chunks of javascript
和一个特定的出口
with a specific export
和一个渲染器，它基本上协调了如何
and a renderer which basically coordinates how
渲染器，它基本上协调了客户端上的东西是如何被补水的
something is rehydrated on the client
我们有一些道具和水化方法
and we have some props and the hydration method
然后在这里面我们什么都没有
and then inside of this we have nothing
但如果我禁用javascript
but if I disabled javascript
我们在这里有一些模板元素
we have some template elements here
因为我们的组件并没有呈现任何东西
because our component didn't render anything
但我们知道，当我们渲染东西时，我们必须传入一些
butwe knew that we have to pass in some
槽的内容，当我们渲染东西的时候
slotted content when we do render something
所以这些对应的是有槽的内容
so these correspond to the slotted content
所以我们的标题将是
so our title is just going to be
的
the
而默认的槽是我们的列表
and the default slot is our list
这些将在javascript启动时被清理掉
and these will be cleaned up when javascript starts
但它们会被保存在内存中
but they'll be held in memory
在水合作用继续进行之前，它们基本上都被送回框架内作为子女。
and before hydration can continue they are essentially
递回给框架，充当儿童
passed back to the framework to act as children
这里也是如此
and same thing here
但有一点不同
but a little different
所以我们有天体槽元素
so we have the astro slot element
天体槽元素告诉我们，在这个元素下面的一切
the astro slot element tells us that everything
下面的元素
below this element
应被视为静态的
should be treated as static
而这就是允许我们在
and this is what allows us to nest
岛屿中的岛屿
islands within islands
也可以相互混合框架
and also mix frameworks with each other
最后
finally
我只是想分享我最喜欢的天体功能
I just wanted to share my favorite astro feature
这就是我们强大的社区
which is our awesome community
我们有一个欣欣向荣的对话社区
we have a thriving discord community
有大量有创造力的人和
with tons of creative people and
很多人愿意提供帮助
lots of people willing to help out
所以，如果你喜欢你今天看到的东西
so if you liked what you saw today
一定要来看看我们在宇航员建造聊天室的情况。
definitely come check us out at astronaut build chat
非常感谢您邀请我
thank you so much for having me
我的名字叫Nate More
my name's nate more
你可以在twitter上关注我，也可以在underscore more上关注我。
you can follow me on twitter and underscore more
和
and
我只想说，我们对自己的决定感到非常高兴
I just gotta say we are so happy with our decision to
成为Vit生态系统的一部分
be part of the vit ecosystem
这真的是最好的地方了
it is really the best place to be
所以再次感谢你们，请查看
so thank you again please check out
天文网络建设
astro com build